https://www.quandago.com/site/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
QuandaGo / QuandaGo – The Connected Experience Platform / Privacy Policy
QuandaGo International B.V. (QuandaGo) , Rivium Quadrant 2, 2909 LC, Capelle aan den IJssel, The Netherlands;
Last revision date: March 30th, 2020 (version 1.02)
Updates: QuandaGo may update this privacy notice from time to time. You may determine when this notice was last updated by referring to the “revision date” found at the top of this web page. If we make material changes to this notice, we will notify you here or by means of notice on our home page.
QuandaGo
Our employees, our customers and the customers of our customers are important to us. In extension with this we take care of the personal data which is processed.
Data protection plays an important role in the fulfilment of our business activities. The safeguarding of personal rights and the compliance with legal regulations on data protection are integral parts.
Knowledge of the requirements of data protection and compliance with the statutory provisions is increasingly a competitive advantage and sets us apart from competitors in the market.
Personal data are processed only when the legitimacy of the processing is ensured. The principles of data processing of personal data, such as data minimization and transparency, are important corporate goals. The required technical and organizational measures for protecting data are based on the European GDPR.
The privacy laws and the interests of our data subjects require ensuring the confidentiality of personal data. The IT systems (including our Websites or Services, human resource system, CRM system) undergo therefore a high level of confidentiality protection.
All employees and the management are aware of their responsibilities when dealing with personal data and support the data protection policy and strategy to the best of their ability and in good conscience.
What does this Privacy notice cover?
This Privacy notice covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website or Services. We use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Website and Services to:
Personalize (e.g. understanding your needs and preferences), provide, maintain and improve our Website or Services,
Allow you to set up a user account and profile,
Contact you about your use of the Website or Services,
Fulfill your requests for or respond to your inquiries regarding certain products, services, events or employment consideration,
Meet legal and regulatory requirements,
Send you our newsletter or other information on products and services, but only if you sign up for it,
Analyze how you use the Website or Services, and
Other purposes where you provide us with explicit consent.
By voluntarily submitting your Personal Information, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy notice.
When you submit Personal Information to this Website, information will not be disclosed to another VANAD Group company unless there is a legitimate interest or you provide us consent to do so.
In some circumstances, QuandaGo may share this Personal Information with third party business partners. We will only use such business partners in order to deliver services to us or on our behalf, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Although very unlikely, in some instances, such as a legal proceeding or court order, QuandaGo may be required to disclose certain information to authorities. QuandaGo shall verify that the authorities who are making the request have legitimate grounds to do so and will only disclose the information specifically requested.
What Personal Information is collected?
We receive and store any information you provide to us. The Personal Information that we would collect from you if you so choose would typically include your name and title, email address, mailing address, telephone and fax numbers, and information about your company.
When a user visits our Websites and clicks on the pages, we collect aggregated data about the path of the user’s visit through the Website. Click streaming is a technology that allows a web site operator to track the paths that visitors take as they access a web site and look at the site’s pages.
We do not intend to collect sensitive information (for example, data relating to race or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, criminal record, physical or mental health or sexual orientation) from our Website visitors. We will, where necessary, obtain your explicit consent to collect and use such information.
Personal Information collected on our Websites may be stored and processed within the European Economic Area or a location on which the European Commission has decided to have an adequate level of data protection.
Data retention
QuandaGo limits the use of Personal Information to the purposes identified in this Notice and for which you provided implicit or explicit consent. In accordance with established policies and procedures, we retain Personal Information for only as long as necessary to fulfill the stated purposes, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law.
Protection of Personal Information
We have established commercially reasonable and appropriate security practices to protect Personal Information we hold in our records from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of the Personal Information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. Notwithstanding that security safeguards are in place to protect Personal Information, we also encourage you to take security measures to protect against unintended intrusions to your personal privacy (i.e., maintain access pass codes and/or PINs in a confidential manner).
Unfortunately, data transmission over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect Personal Information that is transmitted to us by you, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. Thus, any Personal Information transmitted to us is done so at your own risk.
Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you will find cookies at most major websites. Cookies help to tailor information to your preferences and to see which areas of the website are frequented most. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can change your browser settings to refuse cookies.
However, in so doing, you may not be able to fully utilize the Website.
Cookie
Purpose
Type
Lifetime
_ga
Google Analytics; contains a visitor’s unique and random ID number
Performance
2 jaar
_gid
Google Analytics; stores and updates a unique value for each page visited
Performance
24 uur
Visitor_id
The visitor cookie stores a value which is the unique ID for the visitor
Performance
10 jaar
Facebook
Can be used to share information from our website through social media.
Functional -Social
24 uur
Contact and choices regarding personal information
Should you at any time decide that you do not want to continue to receive electronic communications, you will have the ability to unsubscribe or “opt out” from such communications by means of a link provided in each such communication, or if not provided therein, by sending an email to: hello@quandago.com.
If you have any questions about viewing, correcting, updating or deleting information we have on file about you, please send an email to hello@quandago.com.
There is no cost for reasonable access to Personal Information, unless, for example, you require copies of records, or a request is entered more often than once a year. QuandaGo shall advise you of the cost, if any, prior to satisfying your request. Prior to providing you with access to your Personal Information, we may require additional forms of information, including your Personal Information to validate your entitlement to the information being requested.
QuandaGo monitors compliance with its privacy policies and procedures and has procedures to address privacy-related complaints. In this regard, individuals may address their privacy related concerns by contacting QuandaGo’s Privacy Officer.
We shall respond to all inquiries, concerns and/or complaints about its Personal Information handling practices. Every privacy-related complaint will be acknowledged, recorded and investigated, and the results of the investigation will be provided. If a complaint is found to be justified, appropriate measures will be taken including, if necessary, amending our privacy policies and procedures. Please send an email to hello@quandago.com.
The regulatory authority in the Netherlands that oversees the handling of personal information is the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens, please visit https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/
QuandaGo / QuandaGo – The Connected Experience Platform / Privacy Policy
QuandaGo is a cloud customer experience software company focused on contact centers, knowledge management and business automation.
Copyright © QuandaGo International B.V. All Rights Reserved | 2020 | member of the VANAD Group
